Frieren: Beyond Journey's End
At the Northernmost Part of the Continent,
We Arrived at the Place Where
The People of This World Call Heaven.
The Land Where Souls Rest, Aureole.
It's a Place Where Many Souls Gather,
And I Spoke With My Former Comrades There.
- Great Mage Flamme -
Frieren.
I see the capital is in view.
They're going to celebrate
the triumphant return of the heroes.
It will be quite the party.
Sadly, we have to find new jobs
once we make it back home.
You're already thinking about that?
It's important.
Defeating the Demon King
doesn't mean it's the end of our journey.
We still have a long life ahead of us.
New job, huh?
I hope I can find a job
where I get to drink.
Aren't you a priest?
I see.
Frieren.
I'm sure you have a long life ahead,
longer than we can imagine.
I guess so.
Frieren: Beyond Journey's End
Himmel the hero.
Eisen the warrior.
Heiter the priest.
Frieren the mage.
You have done well
in defeating the Demon King.
With this, the age of peace shall begin.
I heard the king is going to build
statues of us at the square.
That said, I doubt they can recreate
my incredibly dashing look.
He sure changed his attitude.
When we started our journey,
he only gave us ten copper coins.
Now now, Frieren.
We get free drinks this time.
That's great, right?
You corrupt priest.
It really is over, isn't it?
Yeah...
Our adventure has ended.
Ten years, is it?
So much has happened.
On the very first day of our journey,
- Himmel and Eisen almost got executed...
- Do it.
- We will scold them! - Shall I lick your shoes?
- Himmel and Eisen almost got executed...
- ...for being rude to the king.
Our adventure almost
ended then and there.
There was also that time when Heiter was
so hungover, he was practically useless.
You look like an undead.
Are you okay?
- Nope.
- No good, huh?
He's always like that once a week.
Compared to those, I was flawless.
- When you got caught by the mimic,
- It's so dark in here! I'm scared!
- I thought about leaving you there.
- Seriously? We warned you so many times.
- So scary! So dark! So scary! So dark!
- How about we just leave this elf here?
Good grief, we only have
lousy memories, don't we?
But it was fun.
I'm glad I went on
an adventure with all of you.
Yeah, I agree.
It was so short, though.
Short?
What are you talking about?
It's ten years.
Look at Heiter,
he's an old man now.
That is rude.
He always was.
It's almost time.
Era Meteor Shower, was it?
A meteor shower that
only happens every 50 years.
It's perfect for the dawn of
a new era of peace.
Beautiful, isn't it?
It's hard to see it in the city.
Read the room,
we're having a moment here.
Then, next time...
I know a better place to see it,
so I'll take you there 50 years from now.
- What is it?
- No.
Nothing.
Sure.
Let's go watch it together.
Well then, I'll be leaving.
What are you going to do after this?
I'm going to continue gathering magic.
The plan is to travel around the central
lands for the next hundred years or so.
Well, I'll come visit every now and then.
The way elves see things
is beyond our comprehension.
You can say that again.
Just how long has she lived?
To her, 50 years or 100 years
might be nothing.
Shadow Dragon's horn?
We don't have that here.
There haven't been sightings of
a Shadow Dragon for
20 to 30 years, after all.
I see. That's a problem,
I need it for summoning.
Come to think of it, we picked one
at the Demon King's castle.
I asked Himmel to keep it, didn't I?
It has an evil aura emanating out of it...
It's not dangerous to my health, is it?
- Dunno.
- Dunno, huh?
It should be time
for the Era Meteor Shower anyway.
Might as well go get it.
The city has changed a lot
since last time.
It should be around here...
Frieren?
Himmel?
- You're so old and wrinkly!
- That's rude, don't you think?
I still look handsome even
at this age, don't I?
It's been 50 years, hasn't it?
You still look the same as
the last time I saw you.
I thought I would never see you again.
Era Meteor Shower, huh?
How nostalgic.
Oh, and about that thing we picked up
at the Demon King's castle...
The Shadow Dragon's horn, right?
I never forgot about it
for even a moment.
It's been emitting an evil aura nonstop
from inside the drawer, after all.
Uh, sorry about that.
You could've just thrown it
in a barn or something.
I could never do that.
You might have left it with me
without much thought,
but to me, it's something important
a dear friend entrusted to me.
It's something that should one day
be returned to you, just like this.
It's not that important though.
Himmel, are you done yet?
You're already bald,
there's nothing to style about it.
There are a lot of things you can do
even when you're bald.
Then, shall we go see the
Era Meteor Shower?
You look much more
dignified now, Heiter.
I'm now a bishop
in the Holy City, after all.
You don't change a single bit, do you?
Don't pat my head.
You don't change much either, Eisen.
Huh. That's how it looks to you?
That's a dwarf for you.
So, where's the place
where we can see it clearly?
Hmm?
Are we going right away?
Isn't it a bit early
for the Era Meteor Shower?
Yeah, it'll take about a week
from here on foot.
It's that far away?
Goodness.
You're so hard on the elderly.
This really brings back memories.
It's just like the good old days.
We traveled around to so many places.
Everything was shining like new.
In those beautiful memories,
every one of you is always there.
You see,
I've been waiting for the day
we all would gather again like this.
Thank you, Frieren.
You allowed me to have
a very exciting adventure one last time.
So beautiful...
I believe Himmel was happy.
Is he?
That girl traveled with Himmel the hero?
How come she doesn't look sad
in the slightest?
So heartless.
Oh my, but we're not sad either.
Act properly, Bishop!
You heartless man!
You're so harsh.
I mean,
I barely knew anything about him...
We only traveled together
for ten years...
I knew human lives
were short...
Why didn't I try to get
to know him better?
Don't pat my head...
Well then, I will be going
back to the Holy City.
Let me have a good look at you two.
This will probably be
the last time I see you both.
Are you ill?
All the drinking is catching up to me.
Must be divine punishment.
If you happen to visit the Holy City,
make sure to offer
some drinks at my grave.
Aren't you scared of dying, Heiter?
We are the party of heroes
that saved the world.
We will definitely live in luxury
in heaven after we die.
That is the reason
why I fought alongside all of you.
You corrupt priest.
Well then, I will be going first.
All right, I will be going as well.
Another trip to search for more spells?
Yeah, there's that as well,
but I also want to learn
more about humans.
I see.
So I'd like to ask you.
I'm a mage, so having a strong
vanguard warrior with me would be great.
Give me a break.
I'm too old to swing an axe now.
Don't make that look, Frieren.
Life still goes on surprisingly
longer past your prime.
I see.
Then, I will see you again, Eisen.
Yes. See you later.
Episode 1: The Journey's End
It's this tree again.
I always get lost in this forest.
Where am I?
20 Years After the Death of Himmel the Hero.
Central Lands, Outskirts of Holy City of Strahl
Are you looking for something?
Is something wrong?
No. I'm looking for a house
belonging to someone named Heiter.
You are our guest, then.
So you're still alive,
corrupt priest.
Turns out it's not easy to die
in a cool manner.
I brought a drink to offer
on your grave.
Do you want to drink it?
I've stopped drinking.
Is that so?
I think it's too late to ask forgiveness
from the goddess by acting good.
Thank you very much.
Who is she?
Her name is Fern.
A war orphan from the southern lands.
That's not like you.
You're not the type
to help people in need.
You're no Himmel.
Frieren, what brings you here?
I was on the way to the Holy City
to buy some stuff.
I'm trying to interact with people
as much as possible on my journey.
Besides, I owe you a lot, Heiter.
So I came to pay them back
before you die.
In that case,
I would like to ask a favor.
Will you take an apprentice?
Fern has the making of a mage.
Could you take her on your journey?
I'm sorry, Heiter.
Anything but that.
She would slow me down.
You know the death rate of
apprentice mages in real fights.
I have no intention of bringing a girl
entrusted to me by a friend to her grave.
I see...
Then, I would like to ask
something else.
This was excavated from
the grave of Ewig the sage.
They say this grimoire contains long-lost
spells of resurrection and immortality.
I doubt such magic
actually exists, though.
I would like you to decipher it
and find out if they are true.
Can you do it?
They're image ciphers, right?
The people back then
really loved them.
Well, I can do that in five to six years.
I see...
But why do you want me
to decipher this?
I thought you weren't afraid of dying.
I have two reasons.
First, I was just acting tough
in front of the two of you back then.
Second, I am more
afraid of death now.
Well, I'm not asking for immortality,
I just want...
I just want a little bit more time.
Besides, the holy scriptures
told us to live a healthy life.
A long life is exactly that, Frieren.
You corrupt priest.
Also,
I don't mind if you do it on the side,
but can you teach Fern some magic?
I'm a priest,
so I'm just not that good at it.
Well, I guess I could do that much.
There you are.
It wasn't easy to find you.
Do you always train in the forest?
So it was hard even for you
to find me, Mistress Frieren.
Master Heiter also told me that
I don't have much of a presence.
Isn't that a good thing?
I guess so.
I knew it.
I could barely detect
the presence of her magic.
She has incredible mana control.
Just how hard has she trained
at such a young age?
Master Heiter told me
that I would be a full-fledged mage
once I could shoot through that boulder.
Huh, Heiter knows what
he's talking about.
You see, that's...
My spell dissipates
before it can reach the rock.
I see.
What kind of training
must I do to improve that?
But before that,
can I ask you something first?
Do you like magic?
Somewhat.
We are quite alike, then.
- Is Fern's training going well?
- Are you trying to act tough again, Heiter?
- Magic really is amazing.
- But it's worth looking at.
You've been collecting nothing
but strange spells.
-I think it would be a waste for you to die now.
- I hope one day I can show them to you.
Episode 2
It Didn't Have to Be Magic…
It didn't have to be magic.