Things were busy that summer.
Perhaps due to all those frequent disasters last year.
Curses were springing up like maggots.
Exorcise. Consume.
Over and over.
Exorcise.
Consume.
It's a taste nobody knows.
The taste of a curse.
Like swallowing a rag used to wipe up shit and vomit.
Exorcise.
Consume.
What I witnessed was nothing out of the ordinary.
Just the ugliness of the masses.
Despite knowing that, I still chose to be
a sorcerer who saves others.
That's what I've been telling myself ever since that day.
Ever since that day.
This building
belonged to the president of a company that ran
a chain of barbecue restaurants in the area.
However, his business suffered a devastating blow
due to the mad cow disease outbreak last July.
Burdened by huge debts,
he committed suicide with his family.
Since then, the mansion has become
a well-known haunted location.
From local school kids to college students
from outside, and even part-timers,
many visit it as a test of courage,
and many of them go missing.
As rumors continued to multiply,
the damage must have kept on escalating.
Rumors around haunted locations and such
do tend to spread rather quickly.
It's unbelievable how fast word gets around
these days thanks to the Internet.
All this just means more work for us sorcerers.
Additionally, three elementary school kids
went missing on their way home.
Their friends, families, or the police
must be out looking for them.
If they get to the mansion, there's a good chance
they might end up as victims themselves.
We have to sever the root
of the problem as soon as possible.
HQ seems to have the same idea.
That's why they sent me along to investigate.
Entering These Premises Is Forbidden!
Many Have Gone Missing!
qweyuooasjdfoashdh
dadnaiosndfas
a
p
e
m 384 60 l 1500 60 1500 200 384 200
Entering These Premises Is Forbidden!
Many Have Gone Missing!
qweyuooasjdfoashdh
dadnaiosndfas
a
p
e
m 384 60 l 1500 60 1500 200 384 200
Entering These Premises Is Forbidden!
Many Have Gone Missing!
qweyuooasjdfoashdh
dadnaiosndfas
a
p
e
m 384 60 l 1500 60 1500 200 384 200
Entering These Premises Is Forbidden!
Many Have Gone Missing!
qweyuooasjdfoashdh
dadnaiosndfas
a
p
e
m 384 60 l 1500 60 1500 200 384 200
Entering These Premises Is Forbidden!
Many Have Gone Missing!
qweyuooasjdfoashdh
dadnaiosndfas
a
p
e
m 384 60 l 1500 60 1500 200 384 200
Entering These Premises Is Forbidden!
Many Have Gone Missing!
qweyuooasjdfoashdh
dadnaiosndfas
a
p
e
m 384 60 l 1500 60 1500 200 384 200
Entering These Premises Is Forbidden!
Many Have Gone Missing!
qweyuooasjdfoashdh
dadnaiosndfas
a
p
e
m 384 60 l 1500 60 1500 200 384 200
Entering These Premises Is Forbidden!
Many Have Gone Missing!
qweyuooasjdfoashdh
dadnaiosndfas
a
p
e
m 384 60 l 1500 60 1500 200 384 200
Entering These Premises Is Forbidden!
Many Have Gone Missing!
qweyuooasjdfoashdh
dadnaiosndfas
a
p
e
m 384 60 l 1500 60 1500 200 384 200
Entering These Premises Is Forbidden!
Many Have Gone Missing!
qweyuooasjdfoashdh
dadnaiosndfas
a
p
e
m 384 60 l 1500 60 1500 200 384 200
Entering These Premises Is Forbidden!
Many Have Gone Missing!
qweyuooasjdfoashdh
dadnaiosndfas
a
p
e
m 384 60 l 1500 60 1500 200 384 200
Entering These Premises Is Forbidden!
Many Have Gone Missing!
qweyuooasjdfoashdh
dadnaiosndfas
a
p
e
m 384 60 l 1500 60 1500 200 384 200
Entering These Premises Is Forbidden!
Many Have Gone Missing!
qweyuooasjdfoashdh
dadnaiosndfas
a
p
e
m 384 60 l 1500 60 1500 200 384 200
Entering These Premises Is Forbidden!
Many Have Gone Missing!
qweyuooasjdfoashdh
dadnaiosndfas
a
p
e
m 384 60 l 1500 60 1500 200 384 200
Entering These Premises Is Forbidden!
Many Have Gone Missing!
qweyuooasjdfoashdh
dadnaiosndfas
a
p
e
m 384 60 l 1500 60 1500 200 384 200
Entering These Premises Is Forbidden!
Many Have Gone Missing!
qweyuooasjdfoashdh
dadnaiosndfas
a
p
e
m 384 60 l 1500 60 1500 200 384 200
Entering These Premises Is Forbidden!
Many Have Gone Missing!
qweyuooasjdfoashdh
dadnaiosndfas
a
p
e
m 384 60 l 1500 60 1500 200 384 200
Entering These Premises Is Forbidden!
Many Have Gone Missing!
qweyuooasjdfoashdh
dadnaiosndfas
a
p
e
Entering These Premises Is Forbidden!
Many Have Gone Missing!
qweyuooasjdfoashdh
dadnaiosndfas
a
p
e
It must be important
if they're willing to pay my fees.
Are you extorting them again?
You make it sound so bad.
Call it negotiation.
We're here.
Let's go, then.
Emerge from the darkness that is darker than black.
Purify that which—
A Veil won't be necessary.
Really?
I don't sense the presence of any curses here.
There's a very good chance that
it's inside the building.
You can cast the Veil later
if we end up attacking it from outside.
Makes sense...
It's unlocked.
Seems like something's blocking the door.
What is all this?
Miss Mei.
It's here.
Its presence is all around us.
Let's get to work.
I don't need that, but I'm guessing you do.
Thank you.
All right.
This place is huge!
Oh, it still has electricity.
Let's take a quick look around the building first.
I'll take this floor. You take the second.
Huh? All by myself?
Is there a problem with that?
N-No, i-it's fine.
Off you go, then.
Okay.
Don't move!
Aha!
Huh!
There!
Here?
Gotcha!
This is the last one.
Ha!
You could be the next big Scream Queen.
Jeez! Please don't startle me like that!
You got startled all on your own.
Are you done exploring the first floor?
Hm?
This is the first floor.
Come again?
I was walking down the first floor hallway.
What? But...
I know I entered a room at the end of the hallway...
Boxes of snacks.
Bags of chips.
Juice cans.
Backpack.
Sweatshirt.
I've seen these three times by now.
Did you notice these marks?
I made them on my way through here.
It would seem that we're
already inside the belly of the beast.
No way...
Seriously?
How long is this hallway?
We've been moving for thirty minutes, so about four kilometers so far.
It's not an innate domain, is it?
It's not.
Those are manifestations of one's mindscape.
Any other ideas?
This must be a barrier.
Correct.
The victims were most likely trapped here too,
and eventually killed by the curse.
Considering it's using techniques like this,
the curse itself should be weak.
If we can just escape this barrier...
Time for a quiz.
How would you break this, Utahime?
This hallway is repeating itself.
At first...
I thought it was like this.
Bold of you to touch them.
I assumed it was shaped like a donut.
But we passed by four of the marks you made, right?
When I counted how many steps apart they were, I got...
122,
203,
157,
and 270 steps.
So the spacing between marks was random.
Interesting.
The interval between repetitions isn't consistent.
So I think... it must be something like this.
The barrier is patching spaces together.
I think if we both run down the hallway
at top speed, then at some point...
It'll break.
Close. Ninety points.
D'oh.
What did I miss?
Don't you think it would be more effective
if we ran in opposite directions?
I get it!
If my patching theory is correct,
running in opposite directions would make it harder
for the curse to hold the barrier together.
Once we have an opening, we might be able to escape!
One hundred points.
It's settled, then.
If this works, I'll be expecting a promotion.
How much do you have in savings?
Pardon?
Never mind. I'll think about it.
Right!
Ready.
Set.
Go!
It worked!
Wait, wha—
I'm here to save your ass, Utahime.
Hidden Inventory / Premature Death
The blue spring of youth stretches out as far as the eye can see
Not a single cloud between us and this breathtaking view
The cicadas' song reverberates off the road
Drowning out your deafening silence
These colors will fade away someday
Even if I etch your scent into my memory
Into the depths of eternity they'll drown
Even today, our youth is shining blue
Even today, our blue shines through
All my wishes and prayers for you
They get close only to get farther
Like whispers of a love untold
Amidst hues of a fleeting summer streaming down my face
Stuck at the back of my throat are words that are a curse to you
"You know we'll meet again, right?"
As my voice gives out on me
Throughout Heaven and Earth
I alone am the honored one
Like grains of stars in the endless galaxy
Throughout Heaven and Earth
I alone am the honored one
Like grains of stars in the endless galaxy
Throughout Heaven and Earth
I alone am the honored one
Slipping through the gaps between my fingers
Throughout Heaven and Earth
I alone am the honored one
Slipping through the gaps between my fingers
Throughout Heaven and Earth
I alone am the honored one
m 1389.33 217.78 l 1793.78 217.78 1794.67 821.33 1389.33 823.11
Jujutsu Tech, Second-Year
Gojo Satoru
You cryin'?
I'm not crying!
m 84 72 l 365.33 69.33 369.33 496 88 493.33
Second-Grade Sorcerer
Iori Utahime
Respect your seniors!
If I was crying, would you console me?
m 1374.67 9.33 l 1910.67 6.67 1912 789.33 1372 786.67
First-Grade Sorcerer
Mei Mei
I would certainly appreciate that.
Nah, I know you wouldn't cry, Miss Mei.
You're strong.
You think?
Gojo! You listen here!
I don't need your hel—
Don't swallow it.
I'll consume it later.
m 1389.33 217.78 l 1793.78 217.78 1794.67 821.33 1389.33 823.11
Jujutsu Tech, Second-Year
Geto Suguru
Satoru, it's not nice to pick on the weak.
What kinda idiot picks on the strong?
You're the one who is picking on her, Geto.
You don't even know it.
Oops.
Utahime!
Are you okay?
m 1218.29 233.14 l 1659.43 232 1664 885.71 1218.29 889.14
Jujutsu Tech, Second-Year
Ieiri Shoko
Shoko!
We hadn't heard from you for two whole days. I was worried.
Shoko! Don't turn out like those two, okay?!
No way I'll become trash like them.
m 166 374 l 298 371 308 752 171 756
TRASH
Look at all the trash over there!
Shut up.
TRASH
Wait, two days?
Ah, was it one of those barriers that
mess with your perception of time?
They're rare, but they do pop up
every now and then.
The whole situation did seem odd
since Miss Mei was with you.
That seems to be the case.
Hm.
Something on your mind?
Oh, I just realized that I technically
worked for two days.
Maybe I should ask for additional compensation.
She's planning another extortion...
Back to the topic, you three.
Where is the Veil?
Next up is the explosion that occurred yesterday
in Hamamatsu, Shizuoka.
_______________________________________________
White
News
GAS PIPELINE EXPLODES DUE TO DEGRADATION
The explosion was caused due to degradation of gas pipes.
One of you told the assistant supervisor that you'd
cast the Veil yourself and left them behind.
Our reporter on the scene...
And then you forgot to do it.
First-Grade Sorcerer
Yaga Masamichi
Who was it?
Teach!
We're better than pointing fingers at each other!
So it was you, Satoru.
Guidance
a
h
u
Is a Veil even necessary in the first place?
Does it even matter if normies see us?
It's not like they can see curses or
cursed techniques, anyway.
Of course it matters.
The primary factor preventing an outbreak
of curses is the citizens' peace of mind.
That's why we have to conceal the
threats they can't see as far as possible.
And that's not all—
Yeah, yeah, I get it.
Looking out for the weak is a pain in the ass, honestly.
Survival of the weakest.
That's the ideal form society should take.
Help the weak and keep the strong in check.
Listen carefully, Satoru.
Sorcerers exist to protect non-sorcerers.
Is that your moral argument? I hate moral arguments.
Excuse me?
Assigning responsibilities to the strong
in the name of some cause is what weak people do.
Get off your high horse and
quit spouting that feel-good bullshit.
Blegh.
I'm outta here.
Why don't we take this outside, Satoru?
You feeling lonely?
Go by yourself.
How long are you going to keep fooling around?
And where's Shoko?
Who knows?
Maybe the crapper?
Whatever.
I'm going to have you two go on a mission together.
What's with the faces?
It's nothing.
I honestly think it's too important
to be assigned to you guys,
but Master Tengen asked for you specifically.
Your mission has two goals.
Master Tengen has found a compatible Star Plasma Vessel.
You are to escort that girl and erase her.
Escort a brat and erase her?
That's right.
Has he finally gone senile?
It's spring. He'll become the principal soon.
It must be getting to his head.
Jokes aside, though—
I'll be the one to decide if I let that off as a joke.
Is this about resetting Master Tengen's technique?
What's that?
What?
Master Tengen has the technique of Immortality,
but that doesn't grant eternal youth.
It wouldn't be an issue if the only change was aging,
but after a certain point,
the technique begins to rewrite the body.
Evolution.
When one ceases to be human
and becomes a higher form of existence.
What's wrong with that? Sounds rad.
According to Master Tengen, those who
reach that state of being have no will of their own.
It means Master Tengen
would cease to be Master Tengen.
Tokyo Metropolitan Jujutsu Technical High School
w4EhT7YjFbRqA2pL9nKoPts6gXc
The barriers of jujutsu schools.
The barriers that form the pillars of jujutsu world.
Even the barriers of all the assistant supervisors.
They are all being strengthened by Master Tengen.
We could hardly maintain our cover
or clean up after missions otherwise.
In the worst-case scenario,
Master Tengen could even become a threat to mankind.
That's why, every five hundred years,
Master Tengen must assimilate the Star Plasma Vessel—
someone who is compatible—
to overwrite the body's information.
Once the body resets, the technique
follows suit and evolution does not happen.
I get it.
Becoming MetalGreymon is fine,
but evolving into SkullGreymon is a problem.
So we need to start over from Koromon.
What? Yeah, whatever, let's go with that.
The Star Plasma Vessel's location has been leaked.
Two groups are after the young girl's life as we speak.
One is the Curse User Group Q,
which seeks to upend jujutsu society
by having Master Tengen lose all reason.
The other is the Star Religious Group
that worships Master Tengen,
known as the Time Vessel Association.
Master Tengen will assimilate the Star Plasma Vessel
during the full moon in two days.
You are to protect the girl until then
and ensure that she reaches Master Tengen!
If you mess this up, the effects will ripple
throughout even human society!
Do not forget that!
Cold
Real talk, though.
I kinda get why Curse User Group Q is after her,
but why would this
Star Religious Group wanna kill the brat?
What they worship is the pure form of Master Tengen.
A merger with the Star Plasma Vessel—
in their minds, an impurity—is simply unacceptable.
The Star Religious Group
is an organization of non-sorcerers.
I don't think we need to worry about them.
The ones to be wary of are Q.
Nah, I'm sure it'll be fine.
We're the strongest, after all.
That's why Master Tengen asked for us specifically, right?
What is it?
You know, Satoru,
I've been wanting to tell you this for a while.
You should be more mindful of the way you talk.
Say what?!
Especially when you're addressing your superiors.
We might end up meeting Master Tengen.
You should be more polite and humble.
You'd scare your juniors less, too.
Hah!
Screw that!
Come on, Satoru.
Never mind. We'll discuss it later.
Coming.
Still alive?
I am, at least.
Would it be our fault if the brat died from that?
Don't blame me.
If you must hate someone, hate Tengen.
m 1400 170 l 1757 170 1757 692.8 1400 692.8
Q Soldier
Kokun
Wha—
Could you please try not to make a scene?
We got chewed out for it just this morning.
This girl is the Star Plasma Vessel?
I know that uniform.
You're sorcerers from Jujutsu Tech.
Hand over the brat.
Or I'll kill you.
Can't hear you.
Come a little closer, will you?
Man, you barely made it.
Impressive.
You're Gojo Satoru, right?
Q Soldier
Bayer
You're famous.
I hear you're strong.
Let me confirm if the rumors are true.
I'm down for that, but let's set a rule.
What rule?
I don't wanna get yelled at for going overboard.
So if you start bawling and apologizing,
I won't kill you.
That's the rule.
Cocky bastard.
And so it begins.
The Star Religious Group
doesn't have the power to fight sorcerers.
But they can pay very well.
That I guarantee.
How about it, Zenin?
Want to get in on the Star Plasma Vessel assassination?
It's not Zenin anymore.
I took my wife's name.
I go by Fushiguro now.
Alright, count me in.
Episode 25
Hidden Inventory
Before the good in me crumbles away entirely
I should have told you everything
In a life descending and dissolving into the night
My tangled emotions flicker like a dim light
"That's just how it is, there's no other way"
Sure, I understand all that
But something's still missing
Why does it all feel so meaningless?
That something I thought could be anywhere
I realized can be found nowhere but here
Those silly little chats were enough for me
Just let me see that blushing face again
And so the moon is dark tonight
Head feels light
Another day I remain unbroken
What was I looking for, again?
My love's wavering
Gotta keep it hidden
And so the moon is dark tonight
Head feels light
Can't get outta bed today
Lemme sleep and sleep 'till the next day
Is this loneliness? Am I crying? So annoying
My already hazy memories are dying
Can't even recall last night
And so the moon is dark tonight
Distorts the light
Where to tomorrow?
You know how sometimes these
random words get stuck in your head?
Like, Privatization of Reclaimed Lands Act?
Exactly! Or like, Corporate Governance!
Please look forward to the next episode,
Hidden Inventory, Part 2!
Next Episode
Hidden Inventory II
You tell us one too, Shoko.
Clippity-Cloppity Carnival.
Whoa!